<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Andy Lee</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Andy Lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Deployment Triggers</title>
      <link>/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</guid>
      <description>Addressed pretty significant page load performance issue founde in larger deployments. Eliminates uses of intensive backend query, replacing it with an asynchronous API call against a lucene index. This change reduces page load from from 2+ minutes to nearly instant, with an incredibly responsive UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EPP1 Final Thoughts</title>
      <link>/publications/epp1-final-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/epp1-final-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>EPP1 Subject Description This subject provides students with the opportunities to collaborate with their peers and the subject&amp;rsquo;s teaching staff, to explore the social practices involved in seeking, obtaining, contributing to and learning from an engineering job or internship. Students are guided in the curation of an e-portfolio that documents their growing understanding of the practices necessary for seeking and obtaining a professional engineering experience. The e-portfolios also document the student&amp;rsquo;s growing capabilities to contribute to a workplace, and to engage in workplace learning focusing particularly on the interpersonal and communication capabilities that may be required in engineering workplaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safety and Ethics</title>
      <link>/publications/safety-and-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/safety-and-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Under construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER STUDIO: Expo-Day</title>
      <link>/publications/last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/last-day/</guid>
      <description>Final Thoughts: Over the last month, I have been involved with an intensive subject: &amp;ldquo;Cyber Security: An Offensive Mindset&amp;rdquo; during summer. Summer studio is a project-based subject aimed for students from different faculties at the University of Technology Sydney, where they can engage in real-world challenges. Utilising a flexible teaching framework, the studios are facilitated by a mix of academic experts and industry partners.
It has been a great pleasure being a part of a cohort that despite being a year or two my senior, established a highly energetic and collaborative environment for the duration of the studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STUDIO PORTFOLIO SUBMISSION</title>
      <link>/publications/studio-portfolio-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/studio-portfolio-submission/</guid>
      <description>ABOUT ME My name is Andy Lee. I’m pursuing a Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) with Diploma in Professional Engineering Practice, majoring in Software and undertaking my 2nd year at UTS. I am quite passionate about cybersecurity and aspire to be a Cyber Security Engineer with focus in incident response (Blue Team). I love problem solving and learning new skillsets, so I dedicated most of my first-year to the UTS Cyber Security Society as an opportunity to learn and gain exposure to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Assessment Activity 2</title>
      <link>/publications/professional-assessment-activity-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/professional-assessment-activity-2/</guid>
      <description> Peer Review </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Assessment Activity 1</title>
      <link>/publications/professional-assessment-activity-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/professional-assessment-activity-1/</guid>
      <description>Peer Review Times are changing and with more and more online applications, an E-portfolio is a great alternative from a traditional CV as it gives the recruiter a more polished overview upon the individual’s skill and experience. During the second week we were tasked to have 3 journals ready for peer review on our E-portfolio. We were tasked to comment on our peer’s E-portfolio with our personal set of criteria, mine is as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplace Learning Readiness</title>
      <link>/publications/workplace-learning-readiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/workplace-learning-readiness/</guid>
      <description>What I aim to learn from the internship As a current second year student studying engineering, I intend to acquire valuable industry insights from professional engineering teams. I am also looking forward to getting hands-on experience in detection, mitigate and secure infrastructure.
Another area of focus would be communication, which entails the ability to communicate information correctly, succinctly and without obstruction. The emerging international landscape means a diverse workforce from a multitude of background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER STUDIO: SPRINT 4</title>
      <link>/publications/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/week-4/</guid>
      <description>Reverse Engineering workshop (SLO 3) On Monday, Ruben, an Application Security manager came to teach us the tools of the trade in Reverse Engineering. Although I have personally touched on this subject area before,but we went straight into the deep-end through experimenting hands-on with Ruben&amp;rsquo;s Reverse Engineering challenges. The tool we used was Binary Ninja, GNU Debugger and X86 Opcode.
^Ruben helping around the studio.
Overall, the workshop was very challenging as we had very little training before, on the otherhand, everyone of us learnt alot especially the mindset when reversing a program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER STUDIO: SPRINT 3</title>
      <link>/publications/week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/week-3/</guid>
      <description>SCRUM REFLECTION (SLO 5) Scrum, a well known method to addess complex adaptive problems was introduced to us from week 1. The execution was simple, the entire class was tasked to stand and report our current progress/difficulties to people we are unfamiliar to. After 6-7 minutes, Larry would choose a random person from each group to present their scrum notes to the class.
^Scrum Notes: Notes on my peer&amp;rsquo;s progress and challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER STUDIO: SPRINT 2</title>
      <link>/publications/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/week-2/</guid>
      <description>PROBLEM STATEMENT (SLO 1) In the midst of modern Cyber arms-race, human error still remains as the number one cause of data breaches. Human error accounts for more than half of all successful Cyber Security breaches, with social engineering being the forefront attack vector still relevant today. I have decided to incorporate this problem into the Web Application testing which we are currently undertaking this week.
ETHINCAL HACKING AND BUG BOUNTIES (SLO 2) Ethical hacking is a controlled method to find out the weaknesses and vulnerabilities existing in a system or network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER STUDIO: SPRINT 1</title>
      <link>/publications/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/week-1/</guid>
      <description>SLO 1, SLO 4 + GROUP REFLECTION A summer studio takes place approximately a month before the usual Autumn university session, utilizing a condensed teaching format of 4 weeks instead of a usual university semester. Out of the many choices to select from, I chose Cybersecurity: An Offensive Mindset as my 6-credit summer course as my personal aim was to find an internship immediately after the holidays.
On the first day (4/02/2019) we were assigned to present upon a Cybersecurity topic of our own choice in groups of 4 to 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment Analysis</title>
      <link>/publications/investment-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/investment-analysis/</guid>
      <description>My investment towards becoming an engineer. ^ Darvin and Norton model illustration
Ever since the first day of my High School engineering class, it has been my goal to have engineering as my profession. It was during year 9, at school, when I was tasked to build a Rube Goldberg machine that automated many human processes. Back then, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t an important thing to think about your future career but for me, I found a great appeal to the logical thought process that engineers possessed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERSTUDIO- CYBER SECURITY: AN OFFENSIVE MINDSET</title>
      <link>/publications/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/about-me/</guid>
      <description>ABOUT ME My name is Andy Lee. I’m pursuing a Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) with Diploma in Professional Engineering Practice, majoring in Software and undertaking my 2nd year at UTS. I am quite passionate about cybersecurity and aspire to be a Cyber Security Engineer with focus in incident response (Blue Team). I love problem solving and learning new skillsets, so I dedicated most of my first-year to the UTS Cyber Security Society as an opportunity to learn and gain exposure to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIWICON 2038AD</title>
      <link>/publications/kiwicon2038ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/kiwicon2038ad/</guid>
      <description>^ Kiwicon stage during welcome ceremony
Compact and surrounded by nature, Wellington, New Zealand reminisces creativity with a powerful mix of culture, nature and cuisine. Kiwicon 2038 was held on the 16th to the 17th of November in Wellington, held at the Michael Fowler Centre. At its core, Kiwicon is a hacker conference that deal with the intricacies of breaking into, breaking around technological systems.
&amp;ldquo;If you&amp;rsquo;re new to hacker conferences, well, we think you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CYSCA 2018</title>
      <link>/publications/cysca2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/cysca2018/</guid>
      <description>INVESTMENT ANALYSIS My investment towards becoming an engineer. Hello there! As this is my first journal entry i would like to share something special, and has made a profound impact towards my perspective upon Cyber Security.
The society is called UTS CyberSec, the one and only Cyber Security society in this University. The club was founded around a two years ago (2017) with its core members coming mostly from IT backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deauther OLED MINI</title>
      <link>/publications/deauther-oled-mini/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/deauther-oled-mini/</guid>
      <description>Paranoid with wireless cameras hidden in the Airbnb? Or the ability to disable your roommate&amp;rsquo;s Netflix stream. The WiFi Deauther OLED MINI is the next leap forward of the Deauther series by DSTIKE, a low-cost WiFi deauthentication project that originates from Spacehuhn.
Hardware-wise, the MINI boasts only ~80mA of power usage, with an extremely compact board design of only 68mm x 28mm. For the user, a SH1106 1.3&amp;rdquo; OLED display and tactile switch provides basic menu control, while power relies upon a common micro-USB cable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Added Docker Build Status Badge to shields.io</title>
      <link>/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</guid>
      <description>Shields.io is a massive library of badges that can be inserted into project README&amp;rsquo;s or websites displaying various statuses (code coverage, health, version, etc). Support for docker was missing the current build health, and was a pretty trivial addition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema.org Structured Data documentation fixes</title>
      <link>/projects/contributions/schema-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/contributions/schema-org/</guid>
      <description>While adding Structured Data to a client&amp;rsquo;s website I found some example JSON that was invalid. Simple contribution to cleanup the user documentation providing syntactically valid JSON documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOSH release for Bamboo &amp; Remote Agents</title>
      <link>/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>BOSH (Bosh Outer SHell) &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; is an open source tool for release engineering, deployment, lifecycle management, and monitoring of distributed systems.&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s amazingly powerful. This examples uses BOSH to provision an Alassian vendor app running on JDK along with the support Postgres database and agents to support it. The releases manages the health of services and will automatically provision, start/stop processes across the various services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Marketplace Plugins</title>
      <link>/projects/creations/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/creations/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker image for Bitbucket CI/CD Pipelines  &#34;shipit&#34;</title>
      <link>/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Provides required dependencies and additional utilities to simplify and codify the process of building, testing and delivering Atlassian plugins all the way to the live marketplace. Executes integration/AUT level tests against all stated compatible versions for the productUploads generated artifact to Atlassian marketplaceProvides corresponding metadata indicating version, release notes, and compatibility</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;]  Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>