<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Andy Lee</title>
    <link>/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Andy Lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WEEK 1: SPRINT 1</title>
      <link>/publications/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/week-1/</guid>
      <description>SLO 1, SLO 4 + GROUP REFLECTION A summer studio takes place approximately a month before the usual Autumn university session, utilizing a condensed teaching format of 4 weeks instead of a usual university semester. Out of the many choices to select from, I chose Cybersecurity: An Offensive Mindset as my 6-credit summer course as my personal aim was to find an internship immediately after the holidays.
On the first day (4/02/2019) we were assigned to present upon a Cybersecurity topic of our own choice in groups of 4 to 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WEEK 2: SPRINT 2</title>
      <link>/publications/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/week-2/</guid>
      <description>ETHICAL HACKING AND BUG BOUNTIES Ethical hacking is a controlled method to find out the weaknesses and vulnerabilities existing in a system or network. In the current technology- centric society, no business is without the use of IT, but such dependency comes at a cost without proper security countermeasures. Mr. Agarwal from TechnoSip Inc summed it up quite well, “Essentially, they&amp;rsquo;re the gatekeepers for the organization, in order to prevent an unethical hacker from inflicting any damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERSTUDIO- CYBER SECURITY: AN OFFENSIVE MINDSET</title>
      <link>/publications/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/about-me/</guid>
      <description>My name is Andy Lee. I’m pursuing a Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) with Diploma in Professional Engineering Practice, majoring in Software and undertaking my 2nd year at UTS. I am quite passionate about cybersecurity and aspire to be a Cyber Security Engineer with focus in incident response (Blue Team). I love problem solving and learning new skillsets, so I dedicated most of my first-year to the UTS Cyber Security Society as an opportunity to learn and gain exposure to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>